Before we move on though, what I do want to cover,
there was a question in the chat,
which is actually a great one,
regarding how do you actually generate
unique keys on the front end.
To be clear, so the thing that I've shown you over this workshop,
let's see, if we take a look at here, okay.
Line 32. As you can see,
this is something that I've cobbled together myself, right?
I'm using ES6 template literals to say,
I'm going to guess at a unique data type which is user,
and then I'm just going to attach the ID to it,
even though I know the ID is not as unique.
So this works, I think,
when you're just prototyping and working on things,
but obviously on an enterprise-grade application,
that becomes a very different matter, right?
Because you're all of a sudden contingent on
the fact that someone made the right choice to scope the name correctly,
and that's not something we ever want to rely on in terms of reducing human error.
So when it comes to actually generating unique IDs,
granted, ideally, your backend is doing that for you,
but in the event you're not actually getting that information,
the NPM module I really highly recommend is the UUID module.
So basically, how it works is you'll install UUID on your project,
and you basically, as you can see here,
you import it at the top of your file,
and then as part of creating the new form.
So actually, this does happen a lot if you're creating on the front-end side especially,
creating new data that you might be sending to the backend.
So you might actually have a case where I'm going to just pseudo-code this,
we're not going to install it because that would just add to the bloat.
But for the sake of demoing this,
let me just go ahead and at the top here.
So you can imagine that what we would do is we would say,
we would copy this line,
say, okay, we're going to use the UUID library.
Then again, assuming we had a new method called add new user,
you could then say this.userList.push,
and when you create that new object,
this is where you're going to go,
the ID is going to be UUID v4 run like this.
Then typically, you probably would have some new user object that you have in
your reactive data that contains like name, again, let's say Ben.
So what I typically do is I just spread out everything from this.newUser,
and then I basically override in case there's any IDs that are attached to it,
this ensures that it's being generated on the fly,
and then that's basically how I would approach generating a unique ID on the front end.